<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Josh Lill&#39;s Sports Blog</title>
    <link>http://j-lill1102.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Josh Lill&#39;s Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://j-lill1102.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://j-lill1102.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://j-lill1102.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my online sports blog! I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to share a lot of interesting stories with all my readers!
Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Josh Lill! I&amp;rsquo;m currently a sophomore at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, double-majoring in broadcasting and sports media communications. My goal in life is to be a sports announcer, but I love blogging and writing about sports as well. Currently, I am a sports announcer for countless sports at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, both on the radio and television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does The Amount of Hits By A Team In The NHL Weigh Into Their Wins?</title>
      <link>http://j-lill1102.github.io/2022/03/31/does-the-amount-of-hits-by-a-team-in-the-nhl-weigh-into-their-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://j-lill1102.github.io/2022/03/31/does-the-amount-of-hits-by-a-team-in-the-nhl-weigh-into-their-wins/</guid>
      <description>Incredible, eye-opening and exhilarating are often words that are used to describe the game of hockey.
As the chilly air of the arena brushes upon your face, your heart beats faster and faster as each moment toward puck-drop passes by. There are so many aspects of this wonderful game that draw sellout crowds all across the United States of America. Whether Alex Ovechkin is breaking scoring titles year after year or Marc Andre-Fleury’s graceful, yet stupendous saves, are taking a crowd’s breath away, the most flashy parts of the game may not be the only driving factors into determining a team’s success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
